[{"question": " hey! new wallet, huh?", "answer": " yeah, it was time. the old condom ring in the leather just doesn\u0092t say \u0091cool\u0092 anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " rachel!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " you just put an empty carton back in the fridge!", "answer": " oh yeah, i know, but the garbage was full.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " third door on the left.", "answer": " right!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " oh! hey, mr. treeger.", "answer": ": hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": ": what are you doing?", "answer": " ummm. oh! i\u0092m sorry.  it\u0092s a little old but\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": ": no! you\u0092re clogging up the chute that i spent a half-hour unclogging!", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry. i didn\u0092t\u0097i don\u0092t come in here a lot.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": ": oh yeah, of course you don\u0092t!", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 19, "asentId": 20}, {"question": ": \u0091cause you\u0092re a little princess! \"daddy, buy me a pizza. daddy, buy me a candy factory. daddy, make the cast of cats sing happy birthday to me\u009a\"", "answer": " i didn\u0092t\u009a i never said that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": ": you think you could make a mess and the big man in coveralls will come in here and clean it up, huh? well, why don\u0092t think of someone else for a change?", "answer": "  okay, i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " whoa-whoa, treeger made you cry?", "answer": " yes! and he said really mean things that were only partly true.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " i\u0092m gonna go down there and teach that guy a lesson.", "answer": " joey, please don\u0092t do that. i think it\u0092s best that we just forget about it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " that\u0092s easy for you to say, you weren\u0092t almost just killed.", "answer": " all right that\u0092s it, school is in session!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": "  my god! is this a gym card?", "answer": " oh yeah, gym member. i try to go four times a week, but i\u0092ve missed the last 1200 times.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " so why don\u0092t you quit?", "answer": " you don\u0092t think i\u0092ve tried? you think i like having 50 dollars taken out of my bank account every month? no, they make you go all the way down there! then they use all of these phrases and peppiness to try and confuse you! then they bring out maria.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " who is maria?", "answer": " oh maria. you can\u0092t say no to her, she\u0092s like this lycra spandex covered gym\u009atreat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " you need me to go down there with you and hold your hand?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " so you\u0092re strong enough to face her on your own?", "answer": " oh no, you\u0092ll have to come.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": ": tribbiani! hold on, i\u0092ll get the plunger.", "answer": " hey! you hold on pal! now you made my friend, rachel, cry. so now, you\u0092re gonna go up there and apologize to her, unless you want me to call the landlord.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": ": and tell him what?", "answer": " have you heard about a little something called, not making girls cry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": ": yeah. well maybe you have heard about the rent stabilization act of 1968!", "answer": " i have actually not heard of that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": ": yeah, well your friends are in violation of it. i\u0092ve been a nice guy up until now, but uh, i don\u0092t need this grief. i\u0092m gonna call the landlord and tell him that monica is illegally subletting here grandmother\u0092s apartment. your friends are outta here pal.", "answer": " why don\u0092t you tell me something i don\u0092t know!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " oh please, somebody tell me i don\u0092t have to go to work today!", "answer": " what\u0092s the matter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " oh, my first massage today is this incredibly gorgeous guy, and every time i see him i just want to do things to him that i\u0092m not allowed to charge for.", "answer": " so do them for free.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oh no, it is forbidden! no-no, mrs. potter fires people for fooling around with clients. and it\u0092s against my oath as a masseuse.", "answer": " they make you take an oath?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " no, i made myself take an oath. yeah, no fooling around with clients and umm, always be prepared. yeah, that one\u0092s actually from the boy scouts, but it just makes good sense.", "answer": " why don\u0092t you just give him to somebody else?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " oh pheebs, is that a new ankle bracelet?", "answer": " wow! and you got a petticure. your feet are all dressed up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " because that\u0092s the only part of you he can see when he\u0092s on the table!", "answer": " you\u0092re gonna do some feet flirtin\u0092!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " then how do you explain the toe ring?!", "answer": " because it\u0092s arabian princess day at work! okay?! leave me alone!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " oh! my hero! what happened?", "answer": " well uh, i went down there and told him that no one treats my friends like that and that he\u0092d better come up here and apologize. i\u0092ll see you later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " what a minute, what did he say?", "answer": " he said that he wasn\u0092t gonna apologize because you guys are living here illegally, so instead what he\u0092s gonna do is have you evicted\u0097i\u0092ll see you later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " what?! you got us evicted!!", "answer": " i told you not to go down there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " well he made rachel cry!", "answer": " rachel always cries!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " now joey, you go down there and you suck up to him. i mean you suck like you\u0092ve never sucked before!", "answer": " all right! i\u0092ll try! but if i can\u0092t, you can stay with chandler and i until you get settled.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " go!!", "answer": " all right, all right, all right.  i mean i\u0092ll have to check with him first, but i\u0092ll think he\u0092ll be cool with it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " whoa-whoa-whoa, hey! now remember what we talked about, you gotta be strong.", "answer": " yes.  yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " one more time, \"hey, don\u0092t you want a washboard stomach and rock hard pecs?\"", "answer": " no! i want a flabby gut and saggy man breasts!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " good! that\u0092s good!", "answer": " okay.   i wanna quit the gym.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " you wanna quit?", "answer": " i wanna quit the gym.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " you do realize that you won\u0092t have access to our new full service swedish spa.", "answer": "  i wanna quit the gym.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " okay, dave in the membership office, handles quitters.  uh, excuse me,  are you a member?", "answer": " me? no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " sorry, members only.", "answer": "  i wanna quit the gym.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": "  so, are you a member of any gym.", "answer": " no! and i\u0092m not gonna be, so you can save you little speech.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": "  wow, you have really pretty feet.", "answer": " these old things.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " would you mind spending some time on my siadic area, it\u0092s been killing me today.", "answer": " you mean the\u0097okay by siadic, you mean the towel covered portion.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " sure, yeah, no i can do that, yeah, because umm, y'know, the muscles in the siadic area can get y\u0092know, real  nice and tight. so umm, tell me rick, how umm, how did you injure the area.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " oh, a 16-hour sit-in for greenpeace.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " ow! did you just bite me?", "answer": " no!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": ": what?", "answer": " please don\u0092t kick monica and rachel out, this wasn\u0092t there fault, it was mine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": ": you want me to kick you guys out instead?", "answer": " no you can\u0092t do that, where would the chick and the duck live?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": ": you have pets!", "answer": " noo-no-no, no, those are nicknames. i\u0092m the chick and chandler is the duck.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": ": huh, i would\u0092ve thought it was the other way around.", "answer": " come on man, just-just let the girls stay, i\u0092ll do whatever you want.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": ": really? you\u0092ll do anything?", "answer": " yeah-yeah, absolutely.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": ": yeah, i\u0092ve got something you can do.", "answer": " what, what is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": ": can you be my dancing partner?", "answer": " that\u0092s not, prison lingo, is it? commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " his dancing partner?!", "answer": " yeah, there\u0092s this superintendent\u0092s dance, the super ball. i don\u0092t know, and he wants to impress marge, this lady super that he\u0092s a crush on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " well, why doesn\u0092t he practice with a girl?", "answer": " well, he\u0092s too shy, he doesn\u0092t thing he\u0092s good enough to dance with girls yet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey! so, did you quit?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " no, i almost did, couldn\u0092t leave ross there without a spotter!", "answer": " wait, now so you joined the gym?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " and that\u0092s funny, why?", "answer": " oh, umm, i was just y\u0092know working out and umm\u009a oh, that\u0092s it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " we\u0092re doomed. okay, they\u0092re gonna take 50 bucks out of our accounts for the rest of our lives. what are we gonna do?", "answer": " well, you could actually go to the gym.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " or! or, we could go to the bank, close our accounts and cut them off at the source.", "answer": " you\u0092re a genius!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " aww, man, now we won\u0092t be bank buddies!", "answer": " now, there\u0092s two reasons.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " ohh, you guys, remember that cute client i told you about? i bit him.", "answer": " where?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " on the touchy.", "answer": " and that\u0092s not against your oath?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " no, i know! i-i\u0092m sorry, but the moment i touch him, i just wanna throw out my old oath and take a new, dirty one.", "answer": " well, next time your massaging him, you should try and distract yourself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " yeah! yeah! yeah! like-like when i\u0092m doing something exciting and i don\u0092t wanna get too excited, i just ahh, y\u0092know try to thing of other things like ah sandwiches, and ah baseball, and ah chandler!", "answer": " thank you, joey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " all right, i\u0092m here, let\u0092s ahh, get this over with.", "answer": ": okay ahh, well, just ahh, follow my lead.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " whoa-whoa, don\u0092t we need to do some kinda preparation first? like ahh, get really drunk?", "answer": ": look come on, eh, just ah, just ah, put your arms around me, eh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": ": ahhhh! i\u0092m sorry!", "answer": " no, it\u0092s okay, but if i\u0092m marge, my breasts are coming out my back.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": ": ahh, forget it! i\u0092ll never be any good at this, my mom was right, i\u0092m just a big potato with arms, and legs, and a head.", "answer": " come on man, you\u0092re not a potato.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": ": i\u0092m sure as hell a dancer, it\u0092s no use marge will never go for me.", "answer": " come on treeger, don\u0092t say that. you just ahh, you just need more practice. here, come on, let\u0092s ahh, let\u0092s try it again. come on.  plus, it was, it was probably mostly my fault, anyway. i mean, y\u0092know, i\u0092m not really that comfortable dancing with a\u0097 we-he!! hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " hey-hey, how goes the dancing? gay yet?", "answer": " ah-ha-ha, you guys owe me big time.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": "  what was that?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " you just did a little dancy thing.", "answer": " no i didn\u0092t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 177, "asentId": 178}, {"question": " yes you did! you did like a little hop.", "answer": " you are soo enjoying this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " no, i\u0092m not! and it wasn\u0092t a hop it was a pademarie.", "answer": "  you know the words! you are so into this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " all right, well maybe i\u0092m enjoying it a little bit. i mean i\u0092m getting pretty good at it.", "answer": " ooh, this is soo sweet, joey our little twinkle-toes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " hey-hey, hold on, this isn\u0092t some kind of like girly dance. all right, it\u0092s like a sport, it\u0092s manly!", "answer": " all right, then show me some manly moves.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " hello.", "answer": " hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " we\u0092d like to close our accounts.", "answer": " close your accounts? is there some kind of problem?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " no-no.", "answer": " no, we\u0092d just like to close them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " okay, ms. lambert handles all our closures.  would you come over here please?", "answer": " hi, i\u0092m karen.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  chandler\u0092s knees. chandler\u0092s\u009a ankles. chandler\u0092s ankle hair.  oh no.  okay, you\u0092re all set.", "answer": " oh wow! that was amazing, was that really just an hour?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " yeah! in\u009a really long hour world.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " ugh, okay, i have an enormous crush on you. but because you\u0092re a client, i can\u0092t ask you out, even though you give me y\u0092know, the feeling.", "answer": " wow! i had no idea! but you know, i could always find another masseuse.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " really?!", "answer": " yeah, really.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " suddenly, i very aware that i\u0092m naked.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " mr. simon\u0092s been waiting for\u0097 oh my god!", "answer": " why wasn\u0092t i offered that? i\u0092d definitely pay more for that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " phoebe, we have rules here, this isn\u0092t that kind of place.", "answer": " oh yeah, oh and i know, but this isn\u0092t what it looks like, \u0091cause rick is my ahh, husband.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " oh really? well, then you\u0092d better tell his other wife, \u0091cause she called three times asking where he is.", "answer": " yes, i will tell her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " so you didn\u0092t leave the bank?", "answer": " no! and somehow, we ended up with a joint checking account.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " what are you ever gonna use that for?!", "answer": " to pay for the gym.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey! so i had a great day, rick and i really hit it off, and we started making out, and then my boss walked in and fired me for being a whore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " what?!", "answer": " you got fired?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " oh my gosh!", "answer": " it\u0092s so weird, i have never been fired from anything before!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " sweety...", "answer": " i just-i just started walking around not knowing what to do next, y\u0092know? i-i started asking people on the street if they wanted massages. then these policemen, thought i was a whore too. it\u0092s been a really bad day, whore wise.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": ": hey duck, is chick here?", "answer": " yeah\u009a bunny-rabbit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": "  so you ah, ready for our last practice?", "answer": ": yeah, but y\u0092know, i think the reason we\u0092re not getting that spin right is because my apartment\u0092s too small.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " look, you wanna use our place?", "answer": ": no, i ahh, had another idea.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " we did it!!", "answer": ": i know, we did it!! hey, that was incredible, huh?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " i know, it was amazing! i mean, we totally nailed it, it was beautiful.", "answer": ": thank you, listen, thanks a lot tribbiani, . oh my god, look at the time, i gotta catch the bus to the ball.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " oh well, okay, good luck.", "answer": ": yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " unless you wanna practice the foxtrot again? or-or the tango?", "answer": ": ahh, thanks but no. you see i-i think i\u0092m ready to dance with girls.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": ": yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " go get \u0091em treeger.", "answer": ": right.  hey, ahh, you wanna come? marge has a girlfriend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": "  really?", "answer": ": yeah, you could dance real good with her, she\u0092s the same size as me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " so it looks like you\u0092ve got some great experience here. let\u0092s see ahh, reason for leaving last job?", "answer": " yeah, they thought i was a whore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " okay, we\u0092ll give a call if anything comes up.", "answer": " great! thank you very much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep4.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}]